<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Google Apps Migration on Nava Solutions</title>
    <link>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/category/google-apps-migration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Google Apps Migration on Nava Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Nava Solutions | All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/category/google-apps-migration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nava Certus pricing change</title>
      <link>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/nava-certus-pricing-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/nava-certus-pricing-change/</guid>
      <description>Google Drive Migration
Prior to releasing Nava Certus in June/July this year, we conducted a study of the cloud storage and data migration market in an effort to determine our pricing strategy. This was not an easy task since there weren’t (and still aren’t) that many commercially available tools for migrating data to cloud storage and specifically to Google Drive.
Still, we were able to get an understanding of the market and as a result set the introductory price to $4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dropbox migration; Cloud migration to premise</title>
      <link>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/dropbox-migration-cloud-migration-to-premise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/dropbox-migration-cloud-migration-to-premise/</guid>
      <description>Nava Certus 1.2 Today, we’re announcing the latest version of Nava Certus. With this release, we bring support for migration to and from Dropbox as well as migration from cloud storage to local premise servers.
We’ve been hard at work trying to realize our goal of making Nava Certus synonymous with cloud storage migration. If you have a request for a particular source or destination, please don’t hesitate to respond in the comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nava Certus 1.1 – Migrate from Google, File Conversion</title>
      <link>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/nava-certus-1-1-migrate-from-google-to-google-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/nava-certus-1-1-migrate-from-google-to-google-drive/</guid>
      <description>Nava Certus
Over the past month, we’ve been working on a few new features for Nava Certus. After a lengthy period of testing, we’re happy to finally announce Nava Certus 1.1
The main features in this release include:
Google Drive Source
Many new use cases are enabled with the addition of the Google Drive Source feature, such as:
 Inter-domain Google Drive migration: In some circumstances, it is necessary to transfer Google Drive data from an account in one domain to another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migration Integrity – Ensuring Chain of Custody with Nava Certus</title>
      <link>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/google-drive-migration-integrity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/google-drive-migration-integrity/</guid>
      <description>If you are planning a Google Drive migration and require assurance that the files at the source are exactly the same as the files at the destination, then you may be interested in our “Migration Integrity” feature.
One of the features that we designed into Nava Certus from the very beginning is called Migration Integrity. While this feature is not the most visible to the user, it is perhaps one of the most important for our enterprise customers that may want to ensure a certain chain-of-custody within the migration process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOWTO: Distributed Google Drive Migration</title>
      <link>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/distributed-google-drive-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/distributed-google-drive-migration/</guid>
      <description>Enjoy cloud storage, migrate to Google Drive
This post is another in a series of posts about Nava Certus, our Google Drive migration tool. Specifically, we show you the Distributed feature in NC. The beauty of distributed migration is that it allows you to get rid of your file server, but at the same time possibly stay in the “basic” tier of Google Drive storage, thus avoiding extra Google Drive storage costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOWTO: Migrate File Server to Google Drive with Nava Certus (Centralized)</title>
      <link>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/centralized-google-drive-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/centralized-google-drive-migration/</guid>
      <description>Google Drive Migration Tool
Do you need to migrate a large quantity of files to Google Drive? Have you tasted the frustration of the “manual” approach? Well, why don’t you try Nava Certus? It is the ultimate Google Drive migration tool. It moves files, copies permissions, recreates the directory hierarchy, and lets you print pretty reports for your boss. And you can take all the credit.
Here we show the “Centralized” configuration, where all files go to a single destination Google Drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video: Nava Certus Demo – Google Drive Migration</title>
      <link>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/video-nava-certus-demo-google-drive-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/video-nava-certus-demo-google-drive-migration/</guid>
      <description>We decided to make this video to answer some basic questions from customers. It is a demo of a file server to Google Drive migration.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nava Certus (Beta) Available for Download</title>
      <link>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/nava-certus-beta-available-for-download/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/nava-certus-beta-available-for-download/</guid>
      <description>We are proud to announce the Beta release of Nava Certus, our powerful Google Drive migration software.
With this version of Nava Certus, you will be able to:
 Migrate files from a file server to a single Google Drive account for centralized sharing Migrate files based on file ownership (Distributed Migration) allowing you to distribute all your files and take advantage of up to 30GB built-in storage in Google Drive for each user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nava Certus(Beta): Google Drive Migration</title>
      <link>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/nava-certus-google-drive-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nava-solutions.netlify.com/blog/nava-certus-google-drive-migration/</guid>
      <description>We have been hard at work over the past months and we’re ready now to share our excitement. As of yesterday, we have released the Beta version of Nava Certus, our powerful migration software enabling you to migrate your file server to Google Drive.
In fact, the product is available as a fully functional trial that you can download for free (up to 1GB). We would love to hear your feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>